Klear Zaylin Madera Luzardo FullStack Developer

✓ klearmadera17@gmail.com

/KlearCj

in /klear-madera

+5491126043675



Profile

I am a unique, fun and adventurous software developer and animal lover. Graduated from Plataforma5, with the solid technical background and incredible soft skills I acquired there, I am ready for my first work experience in the IT world and to keep learning new technologies.

Experience

Tutora backend-CoderHouse, (Part time)

12.2022 - present

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Tutor in charge of resolving students' doubts, correcting challenges, complementing the explanations of the teacher in charge, giving feedback on the work submitted, etc.

Huellitas-NoCountry, (5 weeks) ☑

10.2022 - 12.2022

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Pet adoption site where you can see the list of pets to adopt, apply for adoption and add to favorites, shelters have a dahsboard/CRUD and can receive adoption applications. They have a private chat to communicate. Deployed on AWS.

Magazine WOW-Hogarth Worldwide, (4 weeks)

09.2022 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

- 5 developers, Scrum, Trello.
- Online magazine, dynamic zones, CRUD system based on MongoDB and Strapi (CMS).
- The whole team got the credit for the project's success.

Education

Fullstack Developer, Plataforma 5 🛮

07.2022 - 10.2022

Buenos Aires, Argentina

JavaScript Coding Bootcamp, +800 hrs learning and improving software developmet. Working with agile methodologies, practicing soft skills.

QA Tester, Instituto web

10.2022 - present

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Test planning, Test cases, API test, Bugs reports, White box, Black Box, Unit test, Integration testing.

Habilidades

- HTML	- CSS	- JavaScript	- Node.js
- PostgreSQL	- Sequelize	- MongoDB	- Mongoose
- Strapi	- JWT	- Express.js	- React.js
- Next.js	- Redux	- ChakraUI	- MUI
- Bootstrap	- Git	- Postman	